<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gateway on Steven Lemonier</title>
    <link>https://stevenlemonier.fr/tags/gateway/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gateway on Steven Lemonier</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stevenlemonier.fr/tags/gateway/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Citrix Logon Simulator</title>
      <link>https://stevenlemonier.fr/citrix-logon-simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenlemonier.fr/citrix-logon-simulator/</guid>
      <description>Note: I recommend you to read the following post but if you&amp;rsquo;re only interested by the script: here it is.
An introduction I always wanted to monitor correctly the end-user experience and especially application availability. Like, at any time of the day, can my business-critical resource be opened without any issue? And if there is, at which stage does it fail? Log on to the portal? Application enumeration? At the application launch?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use monitors to leverage your GSLB setup</title>
      <link>https://stevenlemonier.fr/use-monitors-to-leverage-your-gslb-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenlemonier.fr/use-monitors-to-leverage-your-gslb-setup/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar with Citrix ADC&amp;rsquo;s GSLB feature, let me summarize in a few words how this works and might help you with your deployment.
Let&amp;rsquo;s assume you are a medium/large company spread across the globe, with several datacentres (for this example, we&amp;rsquo;ll have one in New York and another one in London), and you want to offer the best user experience to your employees, partners or consultants when they work remotely (in this demo, I&amp;rsquo;ll use Citrix published apps and desktops but it can be adapted to any resources you might need to publish externally through your ADC).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
